scdl.net 2019-02-04

# Symbiosis Centre for Distance Learning (SCDL) Privacy Policy

Symbiosis Centre for Distance Learning (SCDL) Privacy Policy
This Privacy policy sets out how Symbiosis Centre for Distance Learning (SCDL) uses, maintains and
protects any information gathered from “Users” visiting the website www.scdl.net
Symbiosis Centre for Distance Learning (SCDL) may change this policy from time to time by updating this
page. You need to check this page from time to time to ensure that you are aware of the changes.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not
limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, respond to a query or survey, fill
out an online form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make
available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, details such as name, email address,
phone number, contact information and date of birth etc. Users may, however, visit our Site
anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily
submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information,
except that it may limit them from engaging in certain Site related activities
Non-personal identification information
We may also collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with
our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer
used and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating
system used and the details of the Internet service provider utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance the overall User experience. User’s web browser places cookies
on their hard drives for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Users
may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent.
However, if they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
Usage and Protection of collected information
We use the personal identification information primarily to enhance and personalize the overall user
experience, improve the site, to run promotions, surveys and to send periodic emails, if required.
We do not share or sell the data to third parties and adopt industry standard data collection, storage
and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, disclosure or
destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored
on our Site. All the sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a
SSL secured communication channel.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you confirm your acceptance of this policy. Your continued use of the Site following
the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes therein.
